brightstorm.com 2011-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Brightstorm

Effective Date: February 17, 2010 

Brightstorm, Inc. ("Brightstorm") is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of our website located at [www.brightstorm.com](http://www.brightstorm.com/) (the "Site"). Because we wish to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact us at [support@brightstorm.com](mailto:support@brightstorm.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact [TRUSTe](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site and not to the practices of our international affiliates, or any websites maintained by other entities to which we link. Brightstorm is not responsible for the content provided on those websites or information those websites may collect about you.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time and will handle your information in accordance with the version that was in place when you submitted it. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the home page of the Site.

**Your Consent to this Privacy Policy**  
By using the Site and Brightstorm service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as Brightstorm may amend them from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and made a part of, the Brightstorm Terms of Use located [here](http://www.brightstorm.com/corporate/terms-of-service) which governs the use of the Site and the Brightstorm service.

**Our Policy Toward Children**  
Brightstorm does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [support@brightstorm.com](mailto:support@brightstorm.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files immediately.

**Information Collection and Use**

Personal Information  
When you register with us through the Site or order certain products and services from us we will ask you for Personal Information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses. For example, if you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain Personal Information from you on our order form.

How Your Information is Used  
Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our business objectives. We use your registration information to create your account and online profile to enable you to use the Brightstorm service. We use your billing information to bill you for the products or services that you have purchased from us. We also use your Personal Information to:  

  * respond to your requests for additional information
  * provide you with access to content
  * notify you of changes to the Site
  * provide product support, customer services and other communications related to your transactions on our Site or with our products, or newsletters (e.g., reminders about a posting you have made, expirations of postings you have made, or updates to courses you have licensed), to determine if you are eligible to receive certain products, services or promotions, provide you with additional information that may be of interest, including marketing materials, and to support other everyday business purposes, such as product development, job applications, and website administration.

Ability to Opt In and Opt Out  
You have the right to "opt-in" and "opt-out" of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. You may choose not to receive any promotional correspondence or newsletters from Brightstorm. If you opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence or newsletters from Brightstorm, we may still contact you in connection with your continued use of the Brightstorm service. You may opt-out from receiving our promotional correspondences or newsletters by following the unsubscribe link provided within each email communication or going to the "Notifications" tab of your profile and updating your preferences. We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that if you opt-out as described above, we will not be able to remove your Personal Information from our databases or those of our third party service providers (i.e., to which we have already provided your Personal Information as of the date that we implement your opt-out request). See the section below titled "Sharing of Information with Third Parties" for further information regarding how we share your Personal Information.

Collection of Information via Technology  
LogData. When you use the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or online service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include, but is not limited to, your computer's Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to the Site and information you search for on our Site. Cookies. Like many websites, we use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to store your username and login password for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by users and general web traffic on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the service. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your computer's browser, which permit them to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. The collection and use of such information is subject to such third party's privacy policy.  
Clear GIFs. We also use "Clear GIFs" or images to analyze traffic on our Site, and within HTML e-mails to determine whether the e-mails have been opened. Clear GIFs (also called Web Beacons, or Web Bugs) are small images embedded on web-pages and in email communications. We do not use clear GIFs to collect or store any of your Personal Information.

**Sharing of Information with Third Parties**  
We won't share, sell, rent, or trade your Personal Information with a third party other than outlined in this Privacy Policy.

  1. Public Display of Information  
If you participate in community features, your username and any other information you choose to submit will be visible to the public. For example, you may also display your name and contact info through some of these services. In addition, our chat, tips and forums allow you to communicate with members of the online community. Whenever you give out information in public areas on our Site, that information can be collected and used by people you do not know to send you unsolicited messages, so you should not give out Personal Information. Please do not post any personal or sensitive information, including your full name, home address, phone number, financial information or any other information that would enable other users to locate you or contact you. We are not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit in these forums.

  2. Service Providers  
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Site and the services available therein, to provide the services on our behalf and to perform services related to administration of the Site ("Service Providers"). For example, we may partner with other companies to fulfill an order for games, deliver promotional emails, bill you for products and services, or provide customer service. While providing services for us, these companies may access your Personal Information, and are required to use it solely as directed by us for the purpose of our requested service. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

  3. Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information  
We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose non-identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

  4. Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement  
Brightstorm cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Brightstorm or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable. We reserve the right to do any of the foregoing.

  5. Business Transfers  
Brightstorm may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will be notified via a prominent notice on our Site for 30 days after of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

**Changing or Deleting Your Information**  
All registered users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by logging into their account and changing their profile settings with their account. If you completely delete all such information, your account may be deactivated. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. If you have any questions regarding changing or deleting your information, you may contact us at [support@brightstorm.com](mailto:support@brightstorm.com)

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our service directly from our Site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. Brightstorm stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [support@brightstorm.com](mailto:support@brightstorm.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Links to Third Party Websites and Use of AdThis Widget**  
Our Site contains links to other websites which you can choose to visit by clicking on a third party link. Also, when you use an "AdThis" widget to bookmark and share our products and Site with others, you will be taken to a third party website. The fact you can link to another website or online service via the Site is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites or online services you visit and use.

Emailing Friends via the "AdThis" Widget  
Through your use of the "AdThis" widget you are also able to tell a friend about the Site in two ways: (i) by entering for your friend's name and email address in the "email a friend" box; or (ii) using the "import contacts" feature of the AdThis widget. The information that is collected by us via the "email a friend" box is your email address and your friend's email address. This information will be used to send your friend a one time email inviting them to visit our Site or the message you choose to enter. The information you enter into the email a friend box is not stored by us for any purpose. When you use the import contacts feature by clicking the "Import Contacts" button you can provide us with the email addresses of your friends from the email address books you select (e.g., your Google or Yahoo email accounts). We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. We store the email addresses you import for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. You may also be redirected to a third party site in order to share a link to Brightstorm. Please note their privacy policy governs the collection and use of the information you choose to submit on those sites.

Facebook Connect  
Our Site allows users to create an account and login to the Brightstorm service using their Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. Creating an account for the first time through Facebook Connect will prompt users to merge their Brightstorm and Facebook accounts. By using Facebook Connect, you are allowing Brightstorm to access your Facebook account information and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use in your use of the Site via Facebook.

If you are not currently registered as a Brightstorm user and you click on "Sign in Using Facebook," you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and join Brightstorm. We allow users to automatically post recent activity back to Facebook, and give them the option to disable Facebook Connect at any time by logging into "My Profile" and clicking on "My Facebook Profile." Further, you can edit your privacy settings for the reviews that appear on Facebook or disconnect this service by visiting the "Facebook Application Settings" page.

Security  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our registration or order forms via the Site, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, visit [here](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Site, you can email us at [support@brightstorm.com](mailto:support@brightstorm.com).

**International Transfer**  
Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to Brightstorm, please be advised that we transfer Personal Information to the United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

**Contact Us**  
If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail or contact us at:

Brightstorm, Inc.  
155 Montgomery Street, Suite 201  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
Or our customer support form
